<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-07-14T19:11:48-07:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Taylee Nam</title><subtitle>sometimes, I write.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">taking notes</title><link href="/2020/07/11/taking-notes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="taking notes" /><published>2020-07-11T11:35:14-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-11T11:35:14-07:00</updated><id>/2020/07/11/taking-notes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/11/taking-notes.html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/TakingNotes.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;TakingNotes&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A lot of times, I feel like a can of exploding silly string with no exact course, no precise action, no idea what I’m doing except to occupy the space I am in. Except to be here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The silly nature of the string has nothing to do with my own personality although I have been told that I can be, on occasion, silly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I’m here. I’m Taylee Nam and I’m here in this meeting, on this call, in this conversation, in this fight, in this car on the way to get donuts on a Saturday morning, and I’m taking notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is too big and too interesting not to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take people, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are just collections of stories. Stories who make them who they are (or at least who they think they are. Who people &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; are can only be determined in the smallest hours of the night or when there is an indeterminant amount of free stuff offered somewhere to the  also indeterminant, but proportionate number of people who get there first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stories like: the amount of milk you put in your coffee and why. The way you talk about your mother. The way you talk &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt; your mother. The way you talk if you had a mother or if you were raised by a pack of nuns out in South Dakota–I don’t know. Stuff like that happens to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, people turn around and happen to stuff like atomic bombs, artificial sweetener, global pandemics, smartphones and clean water, the concept of a “vacation,” watermelon and sweet little inbred dogs, like mine, who I wouldn’t trade for anything less than world peace and even then, I’d have to really think about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this stuff is all happening all at the same time all under the same weird cosmic construct that we call space and time. And that’s just in our galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, yeah. Obviously, yeah, I’m taking notes. History is happening and I want to remember it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On an unrelated note, have you ever noticed how the sky looks at 4:00pm on any given weekend-day? Delightful.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html"></summary></entry></feed>