<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="4.1.1">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2020-08-21T16:10:48-07:00</updated><id>/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Taylee Nam</title><subtitle>sometimes, I write.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">most people are doing their best</title><link href="/2020/08/21/most-people-are-doing-their-best.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="most people are doing their best" /><published>2020-08-21T16:00:04-07:00</published><updated>2020-08-21T16:00:04-07:00</updated><id>/2020/08/21/most-people-are-doing-their-best</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/08/21/most-people-are-doing-their-best.html">&lt;p&gt;Most people are doing their best. Trying, anyway. I like to think so.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people are washing and chopping and dressing their vegetables, because most people want to be healthier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people are downloading meditation apps to address their childhood wounds.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people try to experience the life-changing magic of tidying up. They throw out clothing and birthday cards and half-used hand creams.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people have access to a recycling can, because most people want to protect the coral reef’s from soda bottles and plastic bags.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people are thinking about donating to the American Cancer Society or an art museum or a political campaign or a local restaurant’s GoFundMe. Most people want to give back.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people aren’t sleeping well at night, because most people care enough about their careers, families, friends–name any structure in society and most likely, you care about it. Or pretend to care, and even that pretense (caring/not caring) will keep you up at night. Are you a fraud? Maybe. Are you worthy of love? Maybe not if you’re a fraud. And etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Most people are attempting to live, laugh, love.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Life is hard, but we have great intentions and we try our best.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do or do not, there is no try.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shut up, Yoda, sir.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Most people are doing their best. Trying, anyway. I like to think so.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">it is about time</title><link href="/2020/07/16/itisabouttime.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="it is about time" /><published>2020-07-16T07:04:04-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-16T07:04:04-07:00</updated><id>/2020/07/16/itisabouttime</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/16/itisabouttime.html">&lt;p&gt;Define your terms. If you are going to argue anything, you must define your terms.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, if I were to try and convince Leo that he is better off not barking at me in order to get my attention, I say:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;“To bark is to express oneself in an annoying and harsh manner. You may not bark at me. End of discussion. Go to your room. You’re grounded.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leo, because he is a dog and does not understand the concept of being grounded nor arguments nor even what b-a-r-k-i-n-g means, would most likely ignore me and go on yapping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Regardless of Leo’s current state of physical existence (and I say current, because I absolutely believe that all dogs go to heaven), the point I’m trying to make is that defining your terms orients you and everyone else within an argument.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Another example: time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;What is time? Depends on your definition, cc: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.wired.com/2010/02/what-is-time/&quot;&gt;Sean Carroll&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nature.com/articles/d41586-018-04558-7&quot;&gt;Carlo Rovelli&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.quantamagazine.org/what-is-time-a-history-of-physics-biology-clocks-and-culture-20200504/&quot;&gt;Quanta Magazine&lt;/a&gt; and yes, I did read** those articles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s how I can best understand time:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is above and around us; we are subject to it, because we choose to be.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is flying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is an illusion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time is totally &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; an illusion, because time is how I know I’ve been scrolling through r/oddlysatisfying for an hour and a half.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And I just think. I don’t know. I guess, I just think, that if you could exist outside of time, then you win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Win, like, everything.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We should figure that out, sometime.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;** &lt;em&gt;Define to read (verb): to glance over lightly for the purpose of citing within one’s blogpost.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Define your terms. If you are going to argue anything, you must define your terms.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">taking notes</title><link href="/2020/07/11/taking-notes.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="taking notes" /><published>2020-07-11T11:35:14-07:00</published><updated>2020-07-11T11:35:14-07:00</updated><id>/2020/07/11/taking-notes</id><content type="html" xml:base="/2020/07/11/taking-notes.html">&lt;p&gt;A lot of times, I feel like a can of exploding silly string with no exact course, no precise action, no idea what I’m doing except to occupy the space I am in. Except to be here.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The silly nature of the string has nothing to do with my own personality although I have been told that I can be, on occasion, silly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I’m here. I’m Taylee Nam and I’m here in this meeting, on this call, in this conversation, in this fight, in this car on the way to get donuts on a Saturday morning, and I’m taking notes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world is too big and too interesting not to.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take people, for example.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;People are just collections of stories. Stories who make them who they are (or at least who they think they are. Who people &lt;em&gt;really&lt;/em&gt; are can only be determined in the smallest hours of the night or when there is an indeterminant amount of free stuff offered somewhere to the  also indeterminant, but proportionate number of people who get there first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stories like: the amount of milk you put in your coffee and why. The way you talk about your mother. The way you talk &lt;em&gt;to&lt;/em&gt; your mother. The way you talk if you had a mother or if you were raised by a pack of nuns out in South Dakota–I don’t know. Stuff like that happens to people.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And then, people turn around and happen to stuff like atomic bombs, artificial sweetener, global pandemics, smartphones and clean water, the concept of a “vacation,” watermelon and sweet little inbred dogs, like mine, who I wouldn’t trade for anything less than world peace and even then, I’d have to really think about it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;All this stuff is all happening all at the same time all under the same weird cosmic construct that we call space and time. And that’s just in our galaxy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So, yeah. Obviously, yeah, I’m taking notes. History is happening and I want to remember it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On an unrelated note, have you ever noticed how the sky looks at 4:00pm on any given weekend-day? Delightful.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A lot of times, I feel like a can of exploding silly string with no exact course, no precise action, no idea what I’m doing except to occupy the space I am in. Except to be here.</summary></entry></feed>